- 姓名  - 查尔斯 麦吉尔
- Name.  - Charles McGill.
探访当事人
Client visit.
约翰尼来啦
Here's Johnny!
嗨 我就知道你会来
Hey, I knew you'd come.
可真是稀客啊
All right. You're a sight for sore eyes.
你气色不错
You're looking good.
吉米
Jimmy.
抱歉 要你大老远赶过来
Sorry you had to come all this way.
远道而来 是吧
It's a long way, right?
- 的确很远  - 抱歉
- It's a long way.  - Yeah. Sorry.
关于阿尔布开克 我只知道两件事
Only two things I know about Albuquerque...
兔八哥应该在那儿左拐的
Bugs bunny should have taken a left turn there.
另外就是 让我试一百次 也拼不对这个词
And give me 100 tries, I'll never be able to spell it.
总之 如你所见
Anyway. As you can see,
我遇到点儿 麻烦
I'm in a... A bit of a pickle.
这是显而易见的
You certainly are.
先不管财产损失和人身攻击的指控
Forget the property damage and assault charges.
你这张脸已经被烙上了性犯罪者的罪名了 吉米
You face being labeled a sex offender, Jimmy.
真要是这样的话
If that happens,
它会跟着你走完一生的
it'll follow you for the rest of your life.
简直是胡扯 懂吗
That is insane, okay?
那 那些都是无耻的捏造 查克
Th... That is a trumped-up load of horse crap, Chuck.
- 行了  - 你是不是要我跟法官说
- Come on.  - Is that what I tell the judge...
无耻的捏造
"Trumped-up load of horse crap"?
我现在不是律师了
I'm not the lawyer here, okay?
但这就跟芝加哥的天窗一样明了
But it was a simple Chicago sunroof.
性犯罪 根本连边都沾不到
Sex offender? That's not even remotely a...
我们来谈谈辩护策略吧 行吗
Let's talk strategy, okay?
我需要你动动魔法
'Cause I need you to work your magic
让这整件事烟消云散
and make this whole situation go poof.
你有辩护计划了吗 有吗 来吧
You got a plan of attack? Huh? Come on.
我知道这对你来说不容易
I know I haven't made it easy for you,
但你 你是大人物
but you are... you are the man!
对吗 我知道你掌握着数不清的法律漏洞
Right? I know you got a million legal loopholes
我们能够乘虚而入 各种各样的技巧 你懂的
that we can dance through... Big bag of tricks, you know?
有什么明确的战术吗
Any clever technicalities, huh?
合理的怀疑战术什么的 行了 查克
And reasonable-doubt type stuff? Come on, Chuck.
我们有 多少年 五年没见面了
I haven't seen you in what, five years?
我们几乎没有你的消息
We barely hear from you.
你现在已经自身难保了 你甚至没法
Now that you're in it up to your neck, you can't even
亲自打电话给我 你叫妈妈打电话给我
call me yourself... you have  mom call me?
是妈妈自己决定打电话给你的
Mom took it upon herself to call you!
我就是让她知道一下我的处境
I was just letting her know where I was.
- 你没在电话里跟她哭诉  - 什么 没有
- You didn't cry to her on the phone?  - What? No.
你没哭着要妈妈帮忙
You didn't cry and beg mom for help?
天哪
What? Jesus!
她就听到了她想听到的
She hears what she wants to hear, okay?
我在库克县监狱
I'm gonna cry on a pay phone
的付费电话上哭诉
in the middle of cook county jail.
上帝啊
Jesus!
我们能谈谈辩护策略了吗
Can we... can we talk strategy here, huh?
听着
Look...
我知道我这个兄弟很糟糕
I know I'm a lousy brother.
我是个大混球 我搞砸了很多事情
I'm a lousy brother. I'm a big screw-up.
要是我是个普通良民
And if I was just a better person,
我不仅不会让你一次次的失望
I would not only stop letting you down...
你知道吗 我甚至不会让我自己失望
You know what? I'd stop letting me down.
这是个时间问题
And it's about time
我会让我们俩脸上都有光的
that I started to make both of us proud.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
- 守卫  - 等等
- Guard.  - Wait.
查克 等等 等等
Chuck, wait, wait, wait, wait.
别 别 你不能现在离我而去
No, no. You can't leave me. No.
要是我出不去的话 我这辈子就完了
If I... if I don't get out of this, my life is over!
既然你认识到了这一点
So long as you understand that.
是的
Yeah.
吉米 要是我帮了你
Jimmy, if I do this...
要是...别让我自取其辱
If... Do not make a fool out of me.
我保证
I promise I won't.
你做的每一件事
Everything you're doing,
你陷入的境况 到此为止
everything you're involved with... that's over.
告诉我该怎么做就行了
Just tell me what to do.
无论什么事 我都照做
Whatever it is, I'll do it.
你说吧
Just say it.
求你了 查克
Please, Chuck?
救我
Help me.
风 骚
师
律
律 师
UnIon
字幕组
翻译:剑大人
后期:Paik
校对:乖乖司徒
谁啊
Hello?
嗨 是我
Hey. It's me.
吉米 老天 现在几点
Jimmy? What's... uh...Jesus, what time is it?
时钟上显示凌晨两点
The clock says 2:00,
但我猜你那儿是胡志明市的时区
but I think that might be Ho Chi Minh's time zone.
什么 怎么回事 查克还好吧
What? What's happening? Is Chuck all right?
是的 查克 查克就是查克 对吧
Yeah. Chuck... Chuck is Chuck, all right?
一切都好
E... everything's all right.
我只是想打个电话给你
I just wanted to call you.
你在干吗
So, uh hey, what you doing?
吉米 不 我没说你坏话
Jimmy... No. I'm not talking dirty to you.
什么
What?
你觉得这是我打你电话的唯一理由吗
Wait, you think that's the only reason
在这个点打你电话
I would call you at this time of night?
我是说 你能不能
I mean, can you just give me...
给我一点信任 行吗
Give me a little bit of credit, okay?
那你也没有说我坏话
And you're not talking dirty to me, either.
- 好的 再见  - 我就知道
- Okay, bye.  - I knew it.
开玩笑 开个玩笑 我逗你呢
Uh, joking. Just... just joking, having fun with you.
我今晚打你电话
I am calling you tonight
就聊一聊家常 没别的
with quality PG phone conversation... PG-13 at worst.
哦哦
Uh-huh.
对天发誓
Hand to God, you know?
要是你现在挂掉电话直接开车过来
Uh, but, uh, if you hang up now and drive straight over,
只在规定的时间里有效
limited time only,
我提供免费的修脚和足浴
I'm offering a free pedicure and foot bath.
真的吗 好吧 下次吧
Is that right? Well, maybe next time.
还有其他的呢
Hey, more for me.
你 大概公务缠身
Uh, you're, uh, probably swamped with work anyways,
就是那个什么 大块头的案件
what, with that big, fat, giant case
就倒在你脚边
falling right into your lap.
- 那是什么案件  - 我不知道
- Which case is that?  - I don't know.
一些 县政府官员什么的 还是别的什么
Some, uh, some county official or something?
报纸上都在报道呢
It was in all the papers.
克雷格 吉特曼
Craig Kettleman.
克雷格 吉特曼 没错
Craig Kettleman, yeah!
你老板从我眼皮子底下
The primo client your dipwad boss
偷走的重要客户
stole right out from under me.
没人偷你的客户 这是吉特曼自己的选择
Nobody stole anybody. The Kettlemans made a choice.
是啊 那个宴会也一样 他们都是歪门邪道
Yeah, so did the donner party when they took that shortcut.
行了 吉米 哈姆林也没那么坏
Come on, Jimmy. Hamlin is not that bad.
我会成为二把手 要是这件事受审的话 所以
And I'm gonna be second chair if it ever goes to trial, so...
为我庆贺吧
Be happy for me.
吉特曼到底骗走了多少钱
Hey, um, how much exactly did Kettleman get away with?
抱歉 在证明有罪之前都是无辜的
Uh, excuse me, innocent until proven guilty?
抱歉 但我是这个国家的纳税人
Uh, excuse me, but I'm a taxpayer in this county.
我觉得我有权知晓
I think I have a right to know.
除此之外 并不是因为我是他的律师什么的
And besides, it's not like I'm his lawyer or anything.
我要睡了 你也一样
I have to go to sleep. So do you.
我知道你明天要上庭
I know you have court in the morning.
他偷了至少一百万 还是一百六十万
He got away with 1 million, 1.6 million, at least?
我不跟你讨论细节问题 晚安
I'm not talking details of the case with you. Goodnight.
你把钱都藏哪儿了
Where do you stash all that dough?
我是说 除了买那艘傻逼船
I mean, besides for buying that idiotic boat.
还在吗 有罪
Hello, guilty.
快挂电话
Hanging up now.
那个人 有可能成为别人的目标
This guy's... yeah, he's probably a target.
有人也许起了邪念
Somebody might get some bad, bad ideas.
你知道 要是吉特曼不好好保管那笔钱
You know, if Kettleman isn't careful with that money,
那他全家都处在危险的境地
I mean his whole family could be in danger.
你说危险 是什么意思
What do you mean, "danger"?
吉米 你为什么这么说
Jimmy, why would you say that?
什么
What?
你说那家人有危险
You said the family might be in danger.
我说了么 我 额
I did? I... oh, I, uh...
我 我喝醉了
I'm... I'm drunk.
我只是 把我想的话说了出来
So, I'm just, uh... I'm thinking out loud.
我正在 整理思路
I'm... I'm up, spinning, uh... Spinning thoughts.
- 你确定  - 是的
- You sure?  - Yeah.
好好好
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh...
我们在法庭见
So, I will see you down in the court bowels Maana.
晚安 金
Goodnight, Kim.
晚安 吉米
Goodnight, Jimmy.
我可不是英雄
I'm no hero.
你好 你已经打通了吉特曼一家
Hello! You've reached team Kettleman!
请为克雷格留言
Please leave a message for Craig...
还有贝茨 沃伦
Betsy. Warren
和乔乔
And Jo Jo
滴声之后
After the beep!
你好 你打通了吉特曼团队
Hello! You've reached team Kettleman!
请留言
Please leave a mess...
吉特曼 你有危险了
Kettlemans, you're in danger.
你有危险了
You're in danger.
- 我 你说什么 - 克雷格 谁呀
- I'm s... I'm sorry. What?  - Craig, who is it?
我不确定 等等
I am not sure. Wait.
再说一遍 拜托
Say... say that again, please.
他们知道那笔钱
They know about your money.
小心
Watch out.
什么 你在说什么
Yeah, what are you trying to say?
这是警告 你们有麻烦了
This is a warning. You're in danger.
他们为钱而来
They're coming for your money.
我是友好的陌生人 你们全家都有危险
This is a friendly stranger. Your whole family's in danger.
那笔钱 他们知道那笔钱
The money... they know about the money!
你信号很差
You have a terrible connection.
我警告你
I'm warning you.
他们知道那笔钱 要小心
They know about your money. Be careful.
- 你能不能  - 换一条通畅的线路
- Do you think... - Can you call back on a better line?
吉特曼 你有危险
Kettlemans, you're in danger.
他们来抢你钱了 再见
They're coming for your money. Bye.
他说什么 我们
What did he say? We're...
有危险 他们来了
In danger. They're coming.
谁
Who...
谁要来
Who's coming?
那好 要不这样 义工再加上个别辅导
Okay, how about this...Time served plus counseling?
- 不行  - 他是初犯
- Can't do it.  - It's his first offense.
- 做不到 麦吉尔  - 做不到 做不到
- Can't do it, McGill.  - "Can't do it." "Can't do it."
你是在跟我合作吗
Would you work with me here?
我听着呢 不是吗
I'm listening, aren't I?
你有一点像痴迷受众
Well, you're kind of a captive audience.
你午饭吃的是什么 一整头烤野兽
What did you eat for lunch... The whole roast beast?
有趣
Funny.
好好好
Okay. Okay.
先听我说完 哇哦
But hear me out. Wow.
他已经有三十分了 那就是六十个学分
The 30 he's done, which is a 60 credit,
加上额外的六十天
plus 60 additional days.
做不到
Can't do it.
最好的协议就是 入狱六个月 加上他拘役的时间
Best offer... six months, plus the time he's done,
要是表现良好 九十天出狱
half time for good behavior... out in 90.
- 这是我的底限  - 这不可能
- That's my final.  - That's never gonna happen.
行了 你是在逗我吗
Oh! Come on. Now, are you joking?
这是最好的交易了 你会接受的
Now, that is the best deal you're gonna get.
我办不到
I can't do it.
你的委托人酒驾冲进购物中心
Your guy drove drunk into a shopping center
撞死了三个人
and killed three people.
等等 什么购物中心 德斯蒙德·罗哈斯
Wait. Shopping center? Desmond Rojas.
持枪抢劫 酒品店
Armed robbery, liquor store.
他用一瓶酒打了收营员
He assaulted a cashier with a bottle of Kahlua.
哦
Oh.
我在想达里尔红木
I was thinking of Daryl Redwood.
是的 好吧 我不好 德斯蒙德·罗哈斯 来吧
Yeah, okay. My bad. Desmond Rojas. Okay, go.
再来一遍
Start over.
我不打算再来一遍
I am not starting over.
我每天在这儿修汽车 七百块一次
I'm busting my nut here every day for 700 a throw,
闻着你的臭屁
inhaling your B.M.,
简直就像是恶魔屁眼
which is straight from Satan's bunghole,
而你连哪一个被告都分不清
and you can't tell one defendant from another?!
九十天 良好表现 就这么办
90 days with good behavior... We're doing this.
好 可以
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
说 照着我的话说一遍 我接受协议
Say it. Say the words, "I accept the deal."
好的 我 我接受 我接受协议
Yeah, I... I accept... I accept the deal.
早安
Good morning.
你这是什么意思 我怎么了
W... what do you mean, what did I mean?
我 我 我告诉你了 我喝醉了
I... I... no, I told you. I... I was drunk. I just...
金 为什么你 为什么你问我这个
Kim, why are you...Why are you asking me this?
该死的
Oh, damn it.
拿着 我真的很急
Here. I'm in a real rush.
我没时间去拿验证
I didn't have time to get the validation.
可以 九块钱
Fine. 9 bucks.
我 我没有
I... I don't have it.
只有五块 求你了
I have 5. Please?
你知道规矩 要么给钱 要么验证
You know the drill... Money or the validation.
听着 这是紧事 懂吗
Look, this is an emergency, okay?
非常非常紧急
A serious, serious emergency.
我非出去不可
I have to get out of here.
我保证 以我爹的名誉发誓
I promise, on the souls of my forefathers,
我一回来就给你贴纸
I will get you the stickers when I come back.
我还会多给你点的 要是你放我走的话
I will get you extra if you just let me go.
行了
Fine!
行了 你就是要我回去拿贴纸是吧
Fine! You're gonna make me walk back and get the stickers?!
我会回去拿贴纸的
I will walk back and get the stickers!
我没逼你干任何事 这都是规矩
I'm not making you do anything. Those are the rules.
要是这样能够让你安心入睡的话
Hey, whatever helps you sleep at night.
去你妈的 怪胎
Screw you, geezer!
收到 出发
Copy that, dispatch.
吉米 你怎么来了
Jimmy. What brought you here?
我 额
Me? Uh...
我收到了警用通话
Uh, I... I was surfing the police scanner.
我听说这条路上出了大事
I heard there was big activity out this way.
这里没你什么事 下次吧
Well, there's no business for you here, so maybe next time.
额 是不是入室抢劫 吉特曼家
Uh, it was a home invasion? Uh, the Kettlemans okay?
不知道
Uh, we don't know.
昨晚一个邻居遛狗时
A neighbor was walking the dog last night
看到前门开着
and saw the front door wide open.
家里被洗劫一空 没找到家里人
The place was ransacked. No sign of the family.
现在还没什么线索 我们仍在调查中
There's no note, so... We're still figuring it out.
我得去干活了
I got to get back.
好好 祝你好运
Yeah, yeah. Of course. Good luck.
你来干嘛
Why did you come here?
我只是在她需要的时候提供一点帮助
I'm just supporting a friend in her time of need.
你想帮忙 那就告诉我
You want to be supportive?
你昨晚为何说那些话
Tell me why you said those things last night.
我只是看着茶叶
I'm just reading tea leaves,
同时想到吉特曼一家需要一个律师
same way I knew the Kettlemans needed a lawyer.
他们有一大笔钱
All that money floating out there...
很明显有人会打起钱的主意
It's logical somebody would come after it.
那么 在同一个夜晚 你为他们担忧 他们 消失了
So, the same night you worry about them, they... Disappear?
是的 太疯狂了 就像雷普利一家
Yeah, it's crazy. It's "Ripley's."
吉米 这不仅仅是贝茨和克雷格
Jimmy, it's not just Craig and Betsy Kettleman...
还有他们的两个孩子
It's their two kids, as well.
你应该 告诉我实情
You would... Say something
要是能帮助找到他们的话 对吗
if you could help find them, right?
我不 我不知道他们发生了什么
I don't... I don't know what happened to them.
真的 我不知道
Really, I d... I don't know.
你在这儿呆的时间越长
The longer you stay here,
我就越要花时间向哈姆林解释
the more explaining I have to do to Hamlin.
我们过会儿再说
I'll talk to you later.
要是有什么我能帮忙的就跟我说
Hey, you'll tell me if there's anything I can do?
一切都会好起来的
Everything is gonna be fine.
会有办法的
It's gonna work out.
好的 会没事的
A-okay. It's gonna be fine.
我是拿乔 说吧
Nacho. Leave it.
是的 我
Uh, yes, I'm, uh...
你那天谈到的那伙人
This is the party you spoke to the other day.
我是真心实意想要帮你
Uh, and I sincerely want to help you.
把你的情形缓和下来 用合法的方式
De-escalate your situation, uh, legally and otherwise.
你一有空就拨打电话1468729
Um, so call me at 146-8729 at your earliest convenience.
越快越好
But soon, please.
我是拿乔 说吧
Nacho. Leave it.
拿乔 嗨
Yeah, Nacho, hi.
我只是想说清楚 我什么都不知道
Uh... Just to clarify,look, I don't know anything.
对谁也没说起过
Uh, I have spoken to no one,
我们之间没有叛徒
and, uh, there are no rats on this ship.
看在大家都卷入其中的份上
But for the sake of everyone involved,
我只是想开启对话
I would just like to open a dialogue.
打我电话 1468729
So... 146-8729.
你一听到留言 就打我电话
Call me when you get this.
要是我以前没提起过
If I didn't say it before,
时间是整件事的关键
time is of the essence on this matter,
我准备挂电话了 要是你想打我电话
so, uh, I'm gonna hang up now...If you're trying to call.
要是占线的话 没有呼叫等待
Uh, there's no call waiting here if you get a busy signal.
1468729
146-8729.
多试几次 我就在这儿
Just keep trying. I'll be here.
我能把你从麻烦里救出来 要是你有麻烦的话
I can put out this fire,if there is a fire.
由于种种阴差阳错 这一切都是一场误会
By hope of hopes, this is all a big misunderstanding.
1468729
146-8729.
有人吗
Hello?
在吗 拿乔
Hello? Nacho?
拿乔
Nacho?
继续走 接着走
Walking. Just walking.
走就对了
Just strolling along.
- 感谢上帝 救命 救命  - 下车 举起手来
- Oh, thank God! Help! Help!  - Down! Show us your hands!
- 停下 趴在地上  - 啊 你们是警察
- Stop! On the ground!  - Oh, you guys are cops?
- 举起手来  - 我膝盖不好 哎呀
- Show us your hands!  - I got bad knees! Ow! Ohh!
警官 别这样
Come on, officers.
你们弄错了 我叫麦吉尔 詹姆斯麦吉尔
You're making a mistake. My name's McGill, James McGill.
我是个律师
I'm an attorney.
轻点 轻点
Easy, easy!
这是他的律师
It's his lawyer.
谁的律师
Whose lawyer?
你确定他找我
You sure he asked for me?
进去还是怎么着
Going in or what?
嗨
Hey.
你找我 我就来了
You asked for me, and I have come.
我告诉你 你这么做是明智的
I want to tell you this was a wise move...
很明智 我来这儿是为了帮助 所有人
Very smart, because I'm here to help... Everyone...
各方利益 尤其是你的
All parties, but mostly you.
这两个警探
Uh, those two detectives...
他们只是对我发牢骚
They just gave me an earful.
他们告诉我的事情 是有问题的
And what they were telling me is... it's problematic.
我还会询问你
I'm gonna pitch it back to you
所以我们是在一条船上
so I know we're on the same page.
一个邻居老太太看到一辆可疑面包车
A neighbor lady saw a suspicious van
停在吉特曼家马路对面
parked across the street from the Kettlemans' house
连续两晚都在
two nights in a row.
她记下了车牌号
She wrote down the license plate.
那是你的车牌
It was your license plate.
警察追踪到了你和你的面包车
Cops tracked your van and you,
经过搜查 发现了地上有血
searched it, and found blood on the floor.
那么问题来了
So... Here we are.
额 他们找来了FBI
Um... Um... They're calling the FBI in on this,
就使得整件事变得联邦化了
which makes it federal.
这可不是好事 拿乔
That's a bad thing, Nacho.
这可糟透了
That's... that's very bad,
但你要是告诉我那家人在哪儿
but if you tell me where the family is,
要是你把他们放出来
if... if you give them up now...
全面合作 深深自责
Full cooperation, deep remorse...
我很有自信帮你减刑
I feel very good about knocking your sentence
最少能降到 有期徒刑十八年
down to the minimum... 18 years.
他们很看重这种友好行为
They take this good-behavior thing very seriously,
所以 我们就从这儿入手
so start here, right here.
告诉我那家人没事
Tell me the family is okay.
告诉我孩子没事
Tell me the kids are okay.
你打算告诉我你的想法和涉案程度吗
Y... you want to tell me your thoughts and weigh in?
这听起来像是个要把你投进监狱的计划
Does this sound like a plan that you can get behind?
你这可怜虫
You miserable piece of shit.
- 你给我下套  - 我什么
- You set me up.  - I what?
你把我的目标告诉了别人
You gave my score to another crew,
你现在就在给我下套
and now you're setting me up.
什么跟什么啊 警察打你了吗
I... what the what? D... did the cops beat you?
你说这话就好像受了脑外伤似的
'Cause you're talking like a person with head trauma.
- 你觉得你很风趣  - 你在说什么
- You think you're funny?  - What are you saying?
你是说这事没你的份
Are you saying that you had nothing to do with this?
停在那里的是你的面包车
That was your van outside the house.
- 你不在车里吗  - 我在车里
- Y... you weren't there?  - Yeah, I was there.
我在熟悉地形
I was casing the place,
找出最佳的侵入和撤出路线
figuring out the best way in and out,
他们入睡的时间 等等
what time they went to bed... all that.
我离开的时候他们都没事 就这样
They were fine when I left. That's it.
你没参与吉特曼的事吗
You had nothing to do with the Kettlemans?
我从来没有进屋过
I was never in the house.
那你车里的血迹是怎么回事
What about the blood in your van?
他们只要做DNA检测
They DNA my ride,
就能发现这是你这叛徒小人的血
all they're gonna find is the blood of your skate-rat twins,
还有你的屎尿
plus whatever piss and shit
是你走漏了风声
you leaked out when you were in there.
从那时起就没有人在面包车里面
Nobody's been in the back of that van since.
我 我不明白
I... I don't understand.
以我的理解是 大律师
Here's what I understand, counselor.
我把我的计划告诉了一个人
I told my plan to one other person.
那个人 就是你
One... you.
现在我坐在这儿 被逮捕
Now here I am, under arrest.
你自己想吧
Go figure.
我根本不知道什么陷害或别的什么人
I don't know anything about a setup or another crew.
你知道吗 我根本不在乎
You know what? I don't even care.
这会儿警察正在调查我的生意
The cops are out there right now, poking into my business,
要是他们发现什么我跟我搭档不利的事
and if they find something on me or my partners, for real,
那你就要遭殃了 真正的遭殃
it's gonna be bad for you... really bad.
糟 有多糟
Bad? Bad as in...
你把我弄出去 就是今天
You get me out of here, today...
不然你就是死路一条
Or you're a dead man.
嘿
Oh, hey.
我问你 知不知情
I asked if you knew anything.
你没告诉我你给头号嫌疑人辩护
You didn't tell me you were representing the lead suspect.
我压根就不知道
I didn't know it at the time.
他说什么了吗
He give up anything?
- 什么  - 他告诉你家人的所在了吗
- What?  - Did he tell you where the family is?
他 他不知情
H... he doesn't know.
这是什么意思 他不知情
What does that mean... he doesn't know?
他退给了别人
He gave them to somebody else?
他不知道 因为不是他干的
He... he doesn't know because he didn't do it.
老天啊 算了吧
Ah, Christ. Give me a break.
伙计们 让我们单独呆一会儿吧
Guys, can you give us just a minute?
吉米 那家人现在真的很危险
Jimmy, that family is in real danger.
你没必要坚持什么保密协议
You don't have to stand behind attorney-client privilege.
我没有
I'm not.
那些人可能被埋进一个盒子里
These people can be buried in a box,
拿一根麦秆呼吸氧气
sucking air through a straw right now.
要是真的是这样 那我很抱歉
And I'm sorry if that's where they are,
但我的当事人没参与
but my guy didn't do it.
你怎么那么确定
How are you so sure?
你知道你该干什么吗
You know what you're gonna do?
你去找你们犯罪现场调查员
You're gonna get your special CSI people, right?
检测一下面包车里的血迹
And you're gonna test the blood from that van,
我百分之一万向你保证
because I guarantee you, one billion percent,
那不是吉特曼一家的
it's not the Kettlemans'.
那是谁的
Whose is it?
反正就不是吉特曼一家的 测试了就知道了
I... It's not the Kettlemans'. Just test it.
那会花好几个礼拜的时间
That'll take weeks,
要是我们能拿到DNA样本来对比的话
if we could even get a DNA sample to compare it to.
好吧 这难道还不简单吗
Well, isn't that convenient?
我们现在不就抓了一个无辜之人么
You've got an innocent man in there right now,
我要求你们立刻释放他并且道歉
who I demand you release with an apology!
现在没其他嫌疑人了
Look, there are no other suspects.
没有证据能指向任何人
There's no evidence that points to anyone else.
这样的话 我要求看犯罪现场
Well, then, I want to see the crime scene,
因为你们这些人肯定漏掉了什么
'cause you guys are missing something.
去你妈的 漏掉什么
Screw you, "missing something."
不 警探们 我认为这是个好主意
No, detectives, I, um... I think that's a good idea.
- 好主意  - 是的
- A good idea?  - Yes.
我认为我们应该邀请麦吉尔先生看看现场
I think we should invite Mr. McGill to the house.
为什么
Why?
就是 为什么
Yeah, why?
那么 我们漏掉了什么
So, what did we miss?
这是他们儿子的房间 沃伦 十二岁
This is the son's room...Warren. 12 years old.
乔乔的房间
Jo Jo's room.
她七岁
She's 7.
好吧 你们要我来解密
All right, you wanted me to crack?
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
但我告诉你嫩 我的当事人没干这事
But I'm telling you... My client didn't do this.
我们知道瓦尔加在屋外
We know Varga was outside the house
就是全家失踪的那晚 这一点是事实
the night the family disappeared. That is a fact.
不管你怎么申明这一点
Advocate for the guy all you want
至少要等我们安全地找回他们
after we get these people back safe.
与此同时 帮帮我们
In the meantime, help us.
娃娃在哪儿
Where's the doll?
你说什么
Where's the what?
有小鞋子 小衣服
Uh, got little shoes, a bunch of clothes,
小桌椅和梳子
a table and chairs, hairbrush,
那娃娃在哪儿 就是跟这些玩具配套的那个
but where's the doll that goes with all this stuff?
这小女孩的每张照片上
In every picture of this little girl,
都抱着同一个娃娃
she's holding the same doll.
- 那么 娃娃在哪儿  - 这有什么关系
- So, where's the doll?  - What does it matter?
娃娃没了 女孩也失踪了
Doll is gone... girl is gone,
这就意味着娃娃和女孩很可能在一块儿
which means doll and girl are most likely together,
也就是说
which means...
我不知道这有什么意义
I have no idea what that means.
就是说小孩并不是被强行带走的
Which means the kid wasn't dragged out of the house.
- 依据事实  - 等等
- Ipso facto...  - Wait. Wait.
你刚刚说什么
What are you saying?
也许是吉特曼一家自己绑架了自己
Maybe the Kettlemans kidnapped themselves.
就是这样 你说完了吧 走吧
That's it. You're... You're... you're done. Let's go.
- 这么推测很合理  - 怎么个合理法
- I... it makes perfect sense. - How does it make sense?
他们干嘛这么做
Why would they do that?
他们投了一百多万美金 没错吧
They stole a million dollars-plus, right?
你想要带着花花钞票跑路
You... you want to get away with all that yummy cash,
你该怎么做 逃跑 不 不行
what do you do? Run? No, you can't.
你一逃跑 人人都知道你有罪
If you run, everyone knows you're guilty. Ah!
但要是你被绑架了 你就是个受害者 对吗
But if you're kidnapped, you're a victim, right?
他们自编自导了这出戏 让每个人都能逃脱
They staged this to throw everyone off.
你们找错方向了
You guys are looking in the wrong place.
谁知道他们逃到加拿大或墨西哥的什么地方了
Who knows how many miles into Mexico or Canada they could be?
你们应该放出风声
You... you got to put the word out.
行了 得了吧
Oh, co... come on.
你认为这是不可能的 对不对
You don't think it's possible I'm right?
有这可能 才怪
It's possible... unlikely.
- 才怪  - 他们的车全在这儿
- Unlikely?  - All their cars are here.
没有记录显示有租车服务到这儿来
There's no record of a taxi or car service to the house,
他们也没坐上任何飞机巴士或火车
and they didn't get on any planes or buses or trains.
- 这些你们都查了  - 没错 都查了
- You checked all that?  - Yes, we checked it.
至于娃娃 这不是新发现了 我们知道它们没了
And the doll... it's not news. We saw it was missing.
那它在哪儿
So where is it?
女孩很害怕 哭喊着
The girl was scared, crying.
歹徒让孩子拿着娃娃别再哭了
Bad guy lets the kid take the doll to shut her up.
什么
What?
我认为这不可能
You don't think that's possible?
我要跟你独自谈谈
I need to talk to you alone.
我要告诉你一些事情
I've got to tell you something on the Q.T.,
我要你答应别对我不安
and promise not to be upset with me.
我不可能做这承诺
No way am I making that promise.
我打电话到吉特曼家
I called the Kettlemans.
我挂了你的电话之后 给他们打了个警告电话
After I hung up with you, I gave them a warning call.
警告电话
A warning call?
是的 我很担心我的当事人
Yeah, I was worried my guy Varga
瓦尔加会对他们的钱下手
was going after their money.
没错 他打算绑架他们
And he was. He was gonna rip them off.
这是我从我们的一次对话里推断出来的
I deduced it from a conversation that we had.
是当事人跟律师之间的对话
It was lawyer to client,
所以你懂的 保密协议
so there was, you know, confidentiality issues.
但我匿名打电话给吉特曼家 警告他们
But I called the Kettlemans anonymously to warn them.
匿名
Anonymously?
你没有 天哪 你没有
You didn't... oh, God, you didn't...
那个变声电话不是你打的 是不是
You didn't do the sex-robot voice, did you?
是我打的 用一根管子 这整件事
I did, with the tube and the whole thing,
有可能把他们吓个半死
which probably scared the living shit out of them,
然后他们跑了 你懂的
and they took off, which, you know,
以"意想不到的结果"结案
file that under "unintended consequences,"
那你 你相信我的话了吗
but you... you believe me now?
- 额  - 好极了
- Uh... - Great.
现在我们必须找到他们
Now we have to find them.
我是说 要是可以 让警察放了瓦尔加
I mean... or, better yet, get the cops to let Varga go
因为我现在可是半条命在他们手里
because right now my ass is on a highway to the danger zone.
为什么你会有危险
Well, why are you in danger?
拿乔 瓦尔加 他没绑架他们
Nacho Varga... he didn't kidnap the family.
但他是个恶棍 十足的恶棍
But he's a bad guy. He's a very bad guy.
要是警察不停的逼他
And if the cops keep pushing him,
他们会问出些什么的
they're gonna find something.
真要是这样的话 他会怪到我头上来
And when that happens, Nacho blames me,
然后他手下的人会整死我的
and then his guys turn me into a meat piata.
吉米 报警吧
Jimmy, tell the police.
不 绝无可能 我不能背叛他
No, there's n... there's no way I'm gonna rat on this guy.
我不可能安全的
I will never be safe.
我必须说服警察我的想法是对的
No, I have to convince the cops that I'm right,
让他们别再追查拿乔了
get them to stop looking at Nacho,
然后抓住在逃的吉特曼一家
and catch the Kettlemans on the run.
要是永远抓不到他们呢
And if they never catch them?
吉特曼一家
The Kettlemans?
你已经见过这些人了 对吧
Well, you've met these people, right?
他们 他们也不是什么盖世神通 对吧
They're... they're not exactly masterminds, right?
要是警察通缉他们 他们会落网的
They will be caught if the cops are looking for them,
你会说服他们的 是吗
so you tell them to, would you?
还有FBI 我听说他们准备插手此事
The FBI, too... I heard they're getting in on this.
FBI怎么会听我指挥
Why would the FBI listen to me?
哈姆林 他们听他的 对不对
Well, Hamlin... They'll listen to him, right?
当地警署 至少 你跟霍华德说说
APD, at least. Y... You... you talk to Howard.
你把整件事解释给他听
You explain things to him.
他对那些人也有影响力
He has clout with these people.
什么 你是拒绝还是
What? Is... is that a no or...
哈姆林绝不会同意的
Hamlin will never agree to it.
吉特曼一家是我的客户
The Kettlemans are our clients.
这是在给他们找罪证
This would mean incriminating them.
现在你明白了吧 为什么人们讨厌律师
Oh, you... you see? This is why people hate lawyers.
这全听哈姆林的 而他肯定不会答应
It's Hamlin's call, and Hamlin will never agree.
就算由我来决定 你知道我也不会答应
And even if it were up to me, you know I couldn't.
抱歉 我只是
I'm sorry. I just...
我懂了
I get it.
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
我去跟拿乔谈谈
I'm gonna go talk to Nacho.
我去跟他说道理
I'll try to make him see reason.
去求他饶命
To beg!
别这样
Come on.
Come on!
嗨
Right. Yeah. Hey.
我是个混蛋 好了吧
I was a jerk, okay?
我欠你的钱 我会还你的
So, I will...I will pay you what I owe you,
还包括利息 求你让我过去
plus interest,if you just let me come through.
我建议你停到其他停车场去吧
I suggest you find parking somewhere else.
别的停车场 哪里有什么别的停车场
Somewhere else, as in... Where somewhere else?
关我屁事
Not my concern.
事实上 这是你的职责
Uh, actually, uh, this is your job,
所以 具体来说 这关你的事
so, by definition, it's your concern.
给我一张停车证 打开这该死的门吧 求你了
So pump out the ticket and open the stupid gate already, please.
我是说 我没时间耗在这里
I mean, I don't have time for this.
好
All...
好吧
All right!
嘿 我就停在这儿
Hey. I'm gonna...I'm gonna park right here.
我知道你不想这么干
I don't think you want to be doing that.
怎么样啊
Oh, yeah?
你打算怎么着 你这儿有船尾填充尿布
What are you gonna do? You got a poop-filled diaper in there?
你想把尿布丢我脸上
Are you gonna throw it at me?
你想一枪打死我吗 死怪胎
You gonna gun me to death, huh, geezer?
哎呀呀呀呀
Ohh! Whoa, ow!
疼X5
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ohh! Ohh!
哎呀
Ow! Ow!
我们在说这一家人 妈妈 爸爸 两个孩子
We're talking about a family... Mom, dad, two kids.
律师有一套他的狗屁理论
Lawyer's got this bullshit theory
说他们子自编自导 带着钱跑路了
about them staging this and running off with the money.
你听说过这种事吗
You know the story?
是的 司库携款潜逃
Yeah, county treasurer embezzled funds.
我在报纸上读到过
I read the paper.
是的 我们有权利判这痞子死刑
Yeah, well, we got this gangbanger dead to rights.
唯一的问题就是你那儿的这人
Only problem is your guy over there.
他必须帮助我们 让这人渣开口认罪
He needs to help us get his scumbag client to talk.
你怎么说 加不加入
So, what do you say? You on board?
帮我们做些好事
Help us do some good.
行
Sure.
好 这是我们的协议 你攻击了他
Okay, here's the deal... You assaulted this man.
行了 我根本没碰他
Give me a break. I barely touched the guy.
是你先对他伸手的
But you laid hands on him first.
手指 我只对他点了点手指
Finger... I laid finger on him.
不管你怎么说
Well, whatever your interpretation,
这也算是攻击
it was still an assault.
现在 这位先生决定不再计较
Now, this gentleman is willing to let this go,
不提出指控 除非你帮我们
not press charges, if you help us out.
你要让你的当事人
You got to get your client
告诉我们他把这家人藏匿在哪儿
to tell us where he has the family stashed.
等等 我就像是个走音的唱片
Wait, guys, I'm the definition of a broken record on this one.
拿乔不是软柿子 懂了吗
Nacho is "not-cho" man, omprendo?
没人带走吉特曼一家 他们自己带走了自己
Nobody took the Kettlemans. The Kettlemans took themselves!
你要是还是坚持这套说辞 有你受的
You're gonna keep playing that line, it's gonna go rough.
你猜怎么着 尽管来吧
You know what? Do your worst.
走吧 我们去 登记
All right, let's go... to booking.
行啊
Yeah, sure.
好
Fine.
完美的一天 完美的落幕
Perfect end to a perfect day.
等等伙计们 我改主意了
Hey, guys, wait a second. I changed my mind.
- 你说什么  - 我不想提出指控
- I'm sorry. What? - I don't want to press charges.
我们说好了的 你要提出指控
We talked about this.You want to press charges.
不不
No. No, I don't.
哥们你在搞什么 我以为你支持我们呢
What are you doing, buddy? I thought you had our backs.
不 我没这么说过 哥们
No, I don't think I said that, buddy.
什么 你有个做好事的机会
So, what... you get a chance to do the right thing
却让它溜走
and you puss out?
是的 这大概是我的损失吧
Yeah. Well, I guess it's my loss.
嘿 卡格尼 莱西
Hey, Cagney, Lacey.
当你们意识到你们错的有多离谱时
When you realize how wrong you are about all this,
我要一个可以吃的道歉
I'll take an edible arrangement as a "sorry."
一个大菠萝
Heavy on the pineapple.
嘿 等等
Hey. Hold up.
你为什么让我摆脱困境
How come you let me off the hook back there?
听着 我要回去工作了
Look, I'm going back to work.
你干嘛不停下 继续向前 干你的工作
Why don't you quit while you're ahead and go on your way?
不 我不这么想 因为
No, I refuse to believe it's because
你身体里可能有一颗类似心的东西
you have something resembling a heart inside your body.
五秒钟前 你的身体里
You're not gonna have a heart inside your body
可没有心
in about five seconds.
我知道 别说了 行吗
Okay, don't tell me, all right?
我知道你干嘛这么做了
I already know why you did it.
是吗 为什么
Yeah? Why is that?
因为你相信我
'Cause you believe me.
那家人绑架了他们自己
That family kidnapped themselves.
好吧 我相信你
All right, I believe you.
我就知道 我就知道
I knew it! I knew it!
终于 有人信我了
Finally, someone believes me!
为什么你会相信我
W... why do you believe me?
我听到了细节 你的推论很合理
I heard the details. Your story makes sense.
那当然 只是
Of course it does! But...
魔鬼代言人 就像警察说的
Devil's advocate... like the cops said,
吉特曼的车还在车库里停着
uh, the Kettlemans' cars are still at their house.
没有他们的离开记录
There's no record of them leaving.
他们是怎么出国的
H... how'd they get out of the country?
他们没有
They didn't.
奇怪的是 他们没离开社区
Odds are, they didn't get out of their neighborhood.
什么 什么 再说一遍
What? What? They... come again?
当我还在费城任职时
Look  when I was still on the job back in Philly,
我们听说过这样一个案子
we had this case...
哇哦 打住打住
Whoa, hold up.Hold up.
任职 你是说警察任职
Now, wait. "On the job," as in you were a cop on the job?
在超级碗之后 赌本消失了
This bookie disappeared after the super bowl...
牛仔队还是钢人队的什么人 带走了六百万的赌资
Cowboys/steelers... took 6 million in bets
当事情败露后 逃出了小镇
and skipped town when things didn't go his way.
人人都以为他逃到了巴哈马的海滩边
Now, everybody thought he was on the beach in the Bahamas
或者死在了泽西的贫瘠之地 这不是重点
or dead in the Jersey pine barrens... wasn't the case.
他就在他那被取消赎回权的房子
He was two doors down from
的两层楼下面
where he lived in a foreclosed house.
在那儿躲了六个月 没人怀疑
Hid there for six months without anyone suspecting.
但是 为什么 干嘛不跑呢
But... but why? Why not run?
每个人都那么想
Now, that's what everybody expects.
呆在家的附近 这是人类本能
It's human nature to want to stay close to home,
要是这个吉特曼想出了这么做的办法
and if this Kettleman figured out how to do it,
那这就是他的诡计
that's what he did.
没人愿意离开家
Nobody wants to leave home.
我知道 这还挺让人兴奋的
I know. It's pretty exciting.
让我们真的卖掉它 好吗
Let's really sell this one. Okay?
让我们这样
Let's do this. And...
嘿是我 听听这个
Hey, it's me. Listen to this.
你听到歌声了吗 我找到你的白痴客户了
You hear that?I found your dumbass clients.
说来话长
I... It's a long story.
我会带他们回他们家的
Look, I'm... I'm taking them back to their place.
我们在那儿见
We'll meet you there.
给我几个小时
G... give me a couple hours.
棒极了 孩子们
That was great, guys.
我想我们在睡前还能再玩一次
Yeah, I think we have time for one more before bed.
- 必须要玩吗  - 噢
- Do we have to?  - Oh.
我不知道你是怎么想
Oh, hey, I don't know about you,
但我还想再玩一会儿
but I would love a little
约翰 雅各布 施密特
"John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt."
对啊你猜怎么着
Yeah, and... and you know what?
这个会很有趣的 是吗 水壶队
Let's really have fun with this one, okay, Kettle team?
让我们继续
Let's do this! And...
约翰尼来啦
Here's Johnny!
你好沃伦
Hey. Hey, Warren.
你好乔乔 抱歉
Hey, Jo Jo. Uh, sorry about that.
我是你们的吉米叔叔 好吗
I'm your uncle Jimmy, all right?
现在你们爸妈要带你们下山了
Now, your parents are gonna take you down the mountain,
回自己家 听上去不错吧
back to your house. That sound good?
- 我们  - 怎么样 他们很兴奋
- Uh, we... - Yeah, see? They're excited.
麦吉尔 我们能过会儿再谈吗
M... Mr. McGill, can we talk about this?
不能 你们不能再呆在这儿了
No, we can't, okay? You're done here.
收拾收拾你的东西
Pack up your stuff, bury your scat,
我们要回去了
'cause we're heading back.
- 文明世界在召唤  - 终于能回去了
- Civilization awaits.  - Finally.
我们 能不能
Uh, look, could... please, could we just
- 谈一谈 好吗  - 你们别无选择
- talk this through, okay? - It's not an option.
你们要么自己去自首
You either do this on your own recognizance
要么警察来把你们拖出去
or the cops come and drag you by your heels.
- 我  - 走吧
- I... - let's go.
- 吉特曼  - 不
- Kettlemans. - No.
- 时光飞逝  - 不
- Time to ship out.  - No!
- 是的  - 不
- Yes, you are!  - No!
- 就是这么回事  - 不是这么回事
- This is happening!  - No, this is not happening!
就是这么回事 是的 吉特曼
Yes, it is! Yes! Kettlemans!
- 不  - 是的 你们非走不可
- No!  - Yes, you are doing this now!
不
No!
没错
Yeah.